# Walid Al Ahmad Khaled

Lebanon, Beirut | P: +96171697871 | walid.alahmadkhaled@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/walid-khaled-5700461b8/

Birth: 1997 (23 old).

## **Computer Science Graduated**

Graduated of computer science major, include knowledge in Artificial intelligence, mobile App, networking(cisco), and junior in web developing, I have built a projects in these field and I'm looking for a role where I can grow and learn from other experienced team members.

My future in 5 years is finishing master in artificial intelligence after that PhD in CS with AI specialization.

#### **EDUCATION**

UNIVERSITY: Lebanon, Beirut

**❖** Modern University of Business and Science

Sep 2018-Aug 2022

Major in Computer Science

Cumulative GPA: 3.60/4.0; Dean's List 2020-2021

Relevant Coursework: Web Developing, Software Engineering; Algorithms; Artificial Intelligence; Networking.

Silesian University of Technology

Poland, Gliwice

Study Abroad in Erasmus Program +1 year.

Feb 2020-Feb 2021

Favorite area of study: Relational Database Management Systems.

Favorite class: Web/Mobile Developing.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Web Developer and System Analysis Intern

Jun 2019 – Sep 2019

- ❖ Build a full System Analysis, manage and organize to a company to build the Hotel web application from scratch, which make the building easy, and much faster for employees and for the managers.
- Developed in-house web application using Flask, HTML/CSS/JS that allowed the company to be public and have more subscriber.

### **VOLUNTEERING & UNIVERSITY PROJECTS**

## VOLUNTEERING In Networking.

Feb 2018

❖ Helped the IT employees to distribute routers and switch to the new labs, divided the IPs VLAN and secure them, which make a hug move in the networking field.

## University Senior Project.

Aug 2021

❖ Built and released a responsive web app using Flask/Python HTML/CSS to a real livestock farmer located in Germany and Lebanon to make the company more public and to communicate between the clients and the employees

### **ACTIVITIES**

### **❖** COMPUTER SCIENCE STUDENTS CLUB

Lebanon, Beirut

Member

Sep 2018 – Present

 Make student discussions on novel computer science concepts and troubleshooting issues and giving a hint/help to the new members or to a needer.

### **ADDITIONAL**

### Technical Skills:

- Microsoft Project,
- Python (FLASK/PYQT5),
- HTML/CSS,
- JavaScript (React).
- SQL.
- Exceptionally skilled at all aspects of Python.
- Strong leadership, communication, and collaboration skills.
- Skilled in critical thinking, logic, and high Concentration.

### Languages:

- Native Arabic;
- Fluent English C1;
- Basic Deutsch A1.

### Certifications & Training:

- Online Course in Front-End Web development,
- ICDL Microsoft Office,
- ICDL Computer/Online Essentials,
- CCNA4 Cisco Networking.